Guide to the Central Washington University Registrar Services, Undergraduate/Graduate Catalogs, Bulletins, and Schedules 1892-2012
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Registrar Services, Undergraduate/Graduate Catalogs, Bulletins, and Schedules
1892-2012
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG007-04-07
Central Washington University. Office of the Registrar
34.0 cubic feet 23 letter sized document cases Some aging and foxing to older volumes
This collection contains college catalogs from Central Washington University and its predecessors from 1892 to the present.
Historical Note
The Office of the Registrar at Washington State Normal School was established in 1917. Prior to that date the office served under the principal of the school as secretary and recorder.
Along with general course catalogs for Central Washington University (and its predecessors), this collection also includes summer catalogs, film catalogs, faculty publication lists, and early reports from the Washington States Normal School's Board of Trustees.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Divided into undergraduate and graduate catalogs and bulletins, then arranged chronologically
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University. Office of the Registrar
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Universities and colleges--Curricula--Catalogs
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
College administrators
- Annual Catalogue, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 1-1)
- Annual Catalogue, 1893-1894 (Box-folder 1-2)
- Annual Catalogue, 1895-1896 (Box-folder 1-3)
- Catalogue, 1898-1899 (Box-folder 1-4)
- Catalogue, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 1-5)
- Catalogue, 1900-1901 (Box-folder 1-6)
- Catalogue, 1901-1902 (Box-folder 1-7)
- Catalogue, 1902-1903 (Box-folder 1-8)
- Catalogue and Bulletin, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 1-9)
- Catalogue, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 1-10)
- Catalogue, 1905-1906 (Box-folder 1-11)
- Catalogue, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 1-12)
- Catalog, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 1-13)
- Catalog and Bulletin of Summer Session, 1908-1909 (Box-folder 1-14)
- Catalog and Bulletin of Summer Session, 1909-1910 (Box-folder 2-1)
- Catalog, Bulletin of Summer Session, and Circular of Information, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 2-2)
- Catalog and Bulletin of Summer Session, Bulletin of Summer Session, Centralia and Eburg, 1911-1912 (Box-folder 2-3)
- Catalog and Summer Session at Centralia, Centralia and Eburg, 1912-1913 (Box-folder 2-4)
- Catalog, Summer Session at Eburg, The Kindergarten, and Library Number, 1913-1914 (Box-folder 2-5)
- Catalog, Summer Session at Centralia, and Announcement of Mid Year Graduation Courses, 1914-1915 (Box-folder 2-6)
- Catalog and Summer Session at Centralia and Eburg, 1915-1916 (Box-folder 2-7)
- Catalog, Summer Session, and Bulletin, Teaching of Beginning Reading, 1916-1917 (Box-folder 2-8)
- Summer Session at Centralia and Eburg, 1918 (Box-folder 3-1)
- Catalog, Extension Department, Summer Quarter, and Supplement to the Quarterly, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 3-2)
- Catalog and Summer Quarter, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 3-3)
- Catalog, Extension Service, and Summer Quarter, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 3-4)
- Catalog, Extension Service, and Summer Quarter, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 3-5)
- Flyer, Summer Quarter, 1923 (Box-folder 3-6)
- Flyer, General Curriculum, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 3-7)
- Catalog, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 3-8)
- Catalog, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 3-9)
- Catalog and Bulletin on Student Teaching, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 3-10)
- Catalog, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 3-11)
- Catalog and Flyer, Announcements, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 3-12)
- Catalog, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 3-13)
- Catalog and Alumni Catalog, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 3-14)
- Catalog and Bulletin on Activity Units in Elementary School, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 3-15)
- Catalog, Bulletin on Education of Primary Teachers, Summer Session, and School Quarterly, Public School Teaching, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 3-16)
- General Catalog, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 4-1)
- General Catalog, Washington State Normal College Bulletin, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 4-2)
- General catalog and Announcement of Correspondence Courses, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 4-3)
- General catalog and College Bulletin CWCE, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 4-4)
- General catalog and Summer Session, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 4-5)
- General catalog and Summer Session, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 4-6)
- General Catalog and The CW-seer, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 4-7)
- General Catalog and Announcement of Correspondence Courses, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 4-8)
- General Catalog and Announcement of Correspondence Courses, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 4-9)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 4-10)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Schedule of Classes, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 5-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Correspondence Courses, and Publications of the Faculty, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 5-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Guide to Extension Services, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 5-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 5-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 5-5)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Correspondence Courses, and Publications of the Faculty, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 5-6)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 6-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 6-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 6-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Bulletin of Information, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 6-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 6-5)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 7-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 7-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 7-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 7-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 8-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 8-2)
- Summer Session catalog and Bulletin of Information, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 8-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 8-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, and Correspondence Courses, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 8-5)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 9-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 9-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 9-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 9-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 10-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 10-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 10-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10-4)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11-1)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Schedule of Spring Evening Classes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11-2)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, Schedule of Winter Evening Classes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11-3)
- General Catalog, Summer Session catalog, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11-4)
- Undergraduate Catalog and Summer Session catalog, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12-1)
- Undergraduate Catalog and Summer Session catalog, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 12-2)
- Undergraduate Catalog and Summer Session catalog, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 12-3)
- University Catalog, Summer Session, Spring Quarter Off-Campus Programs Bulletin, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 13-1)
- University Catalog, Summer Session, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 13-2)
- Summer Session, 1983 (Box-folder 13-3)
- University Catalog, Summer Session, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 13-4)
- Summer Session, 1985 (Box-folder 13-5)
- University Catalog, Summer Session, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 13-6)
- Summer Session, 1987 (Box-folder 13-7)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Winter Class Schedule, and Summer Session, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 14-1)
- Summer Session, 1989 (Box-folder 14-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog and Summer Session, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 14-3)
- Summer Session, 1991 (Box-folder 14-4)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog and Summer Session, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 14-5)
- Summer Session, 1993 (Box-folder 14-6)
- Class Schedules, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 15-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Spring Class Schedule, Summer Session, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 15-2)
- Class Schedules, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 15-3)
- Class Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15-4)
- Class Schedules, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15-5)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 16-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Fall Class Schedule, Summer Class Schedule, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 16-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 16-3)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 17-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 18-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Student Handbook, Summer Session, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 18-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Fall Class Schedule, Summer Session, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 18-3)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 19-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 19-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Summer Session, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 20-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Summer Session, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 20-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, 2010-2012 (Box-folder 20-3)
- Graduate Program, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 21-1)
- Graduate Study Program, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 21-2)
- Graduate Study Program, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 21-3)
- Graduate Study Program, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 21-4)
- Graduate Catalog, 1964 (Box-folder 21-5)
- Graduate Catalog, 1965 (Box-folder 21-6)
- Graduate Catalog, 1966 (Box-folder 21-7)
- Graduate Catalog, 1967 (Box-folder 21-8)
- Graduate Catalog, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21-9)
- Graduate Catalog, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 21-10)
- Graduate Catalog, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 21-11)
- Graduate Catalog, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21-12)
- Graduate Catalog, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 22-1)
- Graduate Catalog, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22-2)
- Graduate Catalog, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22-3)
- Graduate Catalog, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 22-4)
- Graduate Catalog, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22-5)
- Graduate Catalog, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 22-6)
- Graduate Catalog, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 22-7)
- Graduate Catalog, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 22-8)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, Washington State Normal School, 1924-1931- (Box-folder 23-1)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1931-1935- (Box-folder 23-2)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1935-1940- (Box-folder 23-3)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1940-1945- (Box-folder 23-4)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1945-1950- (Box-folder 23-5)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1950-1952- (Box-folder 23-6)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1952-1954- (Box-folder 23-7)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1954-1956- (Box-folder 23-8)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1956-1958- (Box-folder 23-9)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1958-1960- (Box-folder 23-10)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1960-1962- (Box-folder 23-11)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1962-1964- (Box-folder 23-12)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Class Schedules, 1964-1965- (Box-folder 23-13)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Summer Class Schedules, 1965-1969- (Box-folder 23-14)
- Undergraduate/Graduate Catalog, Evening Class Schedules, 1974-1981- (Box-folder 23-15)
- Changes in Course Offerings, 1983-1984- (Box-folder 23-16)
- Continuing Education, Resident Credit and Extension Credit Classes, 1975- (Box-folder 23-17)